While most people are stuck playing financial
defense constantly worried about bills and expenses,
the wealthy are playing offense by strategically
building systems that work for them even
when they are sleeping. My name is
Nick and I spend way too much
time studying the habits and mindsets of
people who have cracked the code on
building serious wealth. If you are tired
of thinking like everyone else and getting
the same mediocre results everyone else gets,
this perspective can change everything. The truth
is most of us were programmed from
childhood to think about money in ways
that virtually guarantee we will stay middle
class forever.